[
     {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 121]?",
      "correctAnswer": "24",
      "options": [
        "23",
        "24",
        "25",
        "26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 122]?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "25",
        "26",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 123]?",
      "correctAnswer": "26",
      "options": [
        "25",
        "26",
        "27",
        "28"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 124]?",
      "correctAnswer": "27",
      "options": [
        "26",
        "27",
        "28",
        "29"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 125]?",
      "correctAnswer": "28",
      "options": [
        "27",
        "28",
        "29",
        "30"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 126]?",
      "correctAnswer": "29",
      "options": [
        "28",
        "29",
        "30",
        "31"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 127]?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "options": [
        "29",
        "30",
        "31",
        "32"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 128]?",
      "correctAnswer": "31",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "31",
        "32",
        "33"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 129]?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "options": [
        "31",
        "32",
        "33",
        "34"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 130]?",
      "correctAnswer": "33",
      "options": [
        "32",
        "33",
        "34",
        "35"
      ]
    }
]